# **YUPAI TANG**

## LOOKING FOR ANY KIND OF FASHION JOB

West Chester, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/YUPAI-TANG/72358bc1118e6494

Working in the fashion industry for more than 20 years. I believed that I have earned extensive market knowledge and an excellent understanding of the industry. I used to own a fashion studio in Taipei for nearly 8 years, opened a couture wedding/evening line is the most important thing I accomplished. I learned every step toward a luxury fashion goods business. Also enjoy all the complicated process to develop a new idea from drafting to workable product. I am both good at couture and ready-to wear collections.

As a fashion designer, brand manager, buyer, my job involved quite a wide range about fashion business management. Each job overlaps the functions of one another. Often I am doing two or three of them at the same time. To me, these roles are very hand-on experiences where you'll literally be executing and performing all the responsibilities. To work for a corporate company has better environment to bring skill into full play. I believe that there are many fashionable needs for my creativity within the fashion industry.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### OWNER/DIRECTOR

JUJUBE TANG FASHION STUDIO - 台北市 - July 2001 to March 2007

(Web site: www.jujubetang.url.tw)

7 employees in the office also with outsourcing. Decision-maker. Strategic business approach analytical. Problem solving. Organizational and communication skills. Detail oriented. Developing pricing and market strategies. Interpreting fashion vision and trends into product lines. Trends setter. Reviewing all products for construction, silhouette, fit and trim details. Buying fabrics. Design gowns face to face for customers. Shoe design and accessory's development. I was then under contract to Jasmine Bridel Company. Went on business trips to Shanghai, Guangzhou, Chongqing, Suzhou, Xiamen in China.

#### CHIEF DESIGNER

CHING-HUA WEDDING SHOP - 台北市 - December 2000 to June 2001

Responsible for the design team. Resolved draping/patterning/ construction/sewing problems. Sample fitting. Established communications with suppliers and customers. Buying materiel. Design the wedding dress for Mr. president's daughter.

## **CO-FOUNDER AND BRAND MANAGER**

BELLATINO WEDDING/EVENING DRESS (WEI-WEI WEDDING SHOP) - 台北市 - April 2000 to November 2000

Created Bellatino brand. Retailing management. Establishing new advertising, logo/image campaign. Bring new concepts. To work independently and within a team and with many different levels of management. Have high level knowledge of construction and fabrics and be able to develop first pattern.

Resolved draping/patterning/ construction/sewing problems. Sample fitting. Arranging fashion show. Established communications with suppliers and customers. Interior decoration involved. Financial analysis and review of sales. React to trends and forecasts.

#### **DESIGNER**

WEI-WEI WEDDING SHOP (BELLATINO WEDDING DRESS) - 台北市 - January 1999 to July 1999

#### **BRAND MANAGER**

FENDI AGENT IN TAIWAN, BRAND MANAGER - 台北市 - June 1998 to December 1998

Frequently contact with agent in Hong Kong. buying analysis, buying new lines in Hong Kong office, customer service, selling techniques, staff management, multi store operations, trends analysis, image advertising, promotion activities, media scheduling, in-store decoration, product's education, fashion show, market planning involved, and translating original documents from English to Chinese. Responsible for the Conduct product training, Category sales analysis, Stock control, Budgeting.

## **EDUCATION**

# **EMBA in TEXTILE MARKETING**

Fu Jen Catholic University - 台北市 2011 to 2011

# **FASHION MERCHANDISING**

MISS WADE'S FASHION MERCHANDISING COLLEGE, - Dallas, TX 1996 to 1997

**SKILLS** 

FSHION DESIGNER, INTERIOR DESIGN, GRAPHICS DESIGNER, MANAGEMENT

**LINKS** 

http://www.jujubetang.com

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

## COMPUTER LITERATURE

Window's, Microsoft Word, Wordperfect, Excel, Outlook, Photoshop, Autocad, Coral Drew, Tajama Digitizing, Lotus, Dos, D Base.